{"items": [{"question": "who projects voice into a wooden dummy", "answer": "ventriloquist", "options": ["ventriloquist", "auricle", "dorsal", "ventricle"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A chamber of the heart that receives blood from an atrium and pumps it to the arteries", "answer": "ventricle", "options": ["endorse", "ventricle", "dorsal", "auricle"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "The externally visible cartilaginous structure of the external ear", "answer": "auricle", "options": ["dorsal", "endorse", "avuncular", "auricle"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Belonging to or on or near the back or upper surface of an animal or organ or part", "answer": "dorsal", "options": ["endorse", "vociferous", "avuncular", "dorsal"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Give support or one's approval to", "answer": "endorse", "options": ["somniferous", "endorse", "avuncular", "vociferous"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Resembling an uncle in kindness or indulgence", "answer": "avuncular", "options": ["insomnia", "avuncular", "somniferous", "vociferous"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Conspicuously and offensively loud", "answer": "vociferous", "options": ["somnolent", "vociferous", "somniferous", "insomnia"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Sleep inducing", "answer": "somniferous", "options": ["insomnia", "somnolent", "somnambulism", "somniferous"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "chronic inability to sleep", "answer": "insomnia", "options": ["perambulate", "somnambulism", "insomnia", "somnolent"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Inclined to drowsiness", "answer": "somnolent", "options": ["amble", "perambulate", "somnambulism", "somnolent"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Walking by a person who is asleep", "answer": "somnambulism", "options": ["amble", "preamble", "perambulate", "somnambulism"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Walk with no particular goal", "answer": "perambulate", "options": ["soporific", "perambulate", "preamble", "amble"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Walk leisurely", "answer": "amble", "options": ["soporific", "articulate", "preamble", "amble"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "preliminary introduction, to a document", "answer": "preamble", "options": ["soporific", "banal", "preamble", "articulate"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Sleep inducing", "answer": "soporific", "options": ["soporific", "ventriloquist", "articulate", "banal"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "state clearly", "answer": "articulate", "options": ["banal", "ventricle", "articulate", "ventriloquist"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "overfamiliar through overuse", "answer": "banal", "options": ["auricle", "ventriloquist", "banal", "ventricle"], "answer_index": 3}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 27.txt", "total": 17}